Thanks for your help. I was too nervous to arrive early.
I will do my best today. I'll do my best. I'll be waiting for you.
I'll be waiting for you.
Please.
It's good, right?
Okay.
I'm nervous. Sorry if I cry. I'll do my best.
Happy birthday!
Thank you!
Policy status!
I'll do my best!
No mercy!
Beezanese
chafter
biang hare
bgive me a check
3,2,1,Let's go!
A feeling that the world is about to begin
Milk time of throbbing emotion
From now on, from now on, from now on, I'll deliver it
You're my destiny
I have to fulfill it to the end
The world
It's starting, perfect, Miki, I'm so happy
It's like I'll never be able to go back.
Still, still, still, still, I'll deliver it
You're my treasure
Ah, in these two hands
I can't hold it all in my hands
It was a lonely story, but the colors
You're the one who gave it to me
I'll keep painting for a long time more
It's not a lie, it's a moment of brilliance
Seino
I have a feeling that today is going to be special
I have a feeling it's going to be special
Say hello, hello, hello
Let's gather our little happiness
Our hello, hello, hello
Shining brightly
We'll meet and talk to each other
and a wonderful dream begins
Melody and rhythm overlap each other
I couldn't tell anyone
Goujonen no Liberty Point
Let's go together to a place not seen on a map
I bet it starts from here
Wonderful love forecast
I hear it's gonna sparkle and shine
I'm so mad at you, aren't I?
I'm just as excited as you are
Chute's going to disappear.
I don't think so.
It's been almost three years since we last saw each other.
I wish we could have been closer.
I want you to notice me.
I want to feel the way you do.
It's okay.
I'm not even aware of it.
We're so alike.
I can't even look at you.
You're embarrassing me.
I don't know what I'd do if I did.
This...
For a long, long time.
I've always loved you.
I want to be dyed by your eyes.
Time is of the essence.
Look only at me
I'm in love with you
Baby my love
What a fantasy of the future
I wonder if you'll notice
We're...
Friends Zipper
Pleased to meet you.
My favorite thing about Karen is that no matter what kind of one-liner she does, she always gets the biggest laugh out of me.
I love it!
I love you!
Thank you very much. Congratulations.
Thank you.
Thank you. And here is the star of the show today.
Yes.
This is Karen Matsumoto, who is in charge of baby pink.
Oh my God, I'm laughing. I'm nervous.
I'm so nervous. I'm so nervous,
I forgot all the choreography I had seen during the rehearsal,
Please keep smiling even if I fail.
I'm counting on you.
Crackle, crackle, crackle.
Yes, I know. And so, the Matsumoto Karen Birthday Festival has begun!
Yay!
So, Karen-tan, first of all, how do you like this view?
Oh, it was amazing. So much baby pink.
It's so cute.
So cute.
It's cute.
Thank you.Thank you.
So, here we are at the special birthday event, Karen Matsumoto Produce Time!
Yay!
So, Karen, can I leave it to you from here?
I'll do my best!
Do your best!
Wait for me!
I'll do my best!
Bye bye!
Thank you for watching!
1.2.3.4.5.6.7.8.9.10.11.12.13.14.15.16.1 7.18.19.20.21.22.23.24.25.26.27.28.29.30 .31.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32. 32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.3 2.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32. 32.32.32.32.32.32.32.3 2.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.
32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.3 2.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32 .32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32. 32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.3 2.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32. 32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.3 2.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32.32 .32.32.32.32.32.
When it comes to happy, all love comes true.
I have a feeling that I'm going to be very happy!
I'm almost there
It's not a heart that hears a wish
It's not the heart that hears the wish, it's the heart that falls down
It's a secret, I'm a wizard
Pink blush on my cheeks
Today's lipstick made me cry
Sprinkled with perfume too sweet
The moment I mingle with the lullaby
I'm Cinderella, right?
I'm not living for someone else
I'm living my life for me
I want to love you to the depths of my heart
I want to love you
Happy place
ou me
You came in
me
Wh...
Happy scene. It's about to shine.
It's about to shine
Okay, I don't know, maybe it's a love story that starts now.
I don't want a love story. I want something real.
I don't want a month long story. That's just not enough time.
I'm a real person every day. I like it that way. Sorry.
Shut up.
Let's have the luxury of being carefree.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet.
Skinny skinny skinny skinny
You from me who's scared
Dororikiri sweet
In one sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet year
Let's have the luxury of taking it easy
The cutest part of me
Good day, see you soon.
Did you notice that?
Thirty years after I was born, the first words I heard were.
I don't remember them, of course.
But you must have been happy.
That means you haven't changed a bit.
It's still the same inside.
I'll leave it at that.
Even when I can't see you, I know how you look.
Even when I don't see you, I know how you look and how weird you are.
Tell him he's cute.
Tell me I'm really cute.
You know the cutest thing about me.
You're the most amazing... amazing... amazing...
And you know I'm the cutest thing you know.
And I'm noticing it, too
You're noticing the cutest thing about me.
Hey, I'm noticing that you're really a super lucky guy
And I know that you still think so after all these years
I've noticed it too
You're noticing the cutest thing about me
And you're the most amazing, amazing, amazing
And I'm the cutest thing you know
I've noticed that, too.
And I love my family.
I always want to give my brother, my mom, my dad.
I always want to give good food to my brother and my mom and my dad.
And my fans.
I always want to give good food to everyone.
You know what I mean?
I love them so much.
I want them to eat good food and smile.
You know what I like about you?
I don't have that.
When Karen is happy.
I want everyone to be really happy with me.
I'm sure I'm making them happy.
They love me so much that they think I'm alive.
They love me so much.
But Karen also loves me to the point where I think she's born me.
She loves you to the level of luck.
So when you're not seeing her.
At school or work or whatever.
I always feel like I don't like it when people say bad things about me at school or at work or whatever when they're not seeing me.
That's how raw I am.
That's why I'm able to do my best because of you guys.
I want everyone to think that I can do my best in anything because of you.
I will continue to do my best.
I'm going to sing a song after this.
I'm going to sing a song after this, and I'd like to hear what you think.
"Karen, are you cute today? She'll ask you.
Please tell me I'm cute without my voice.
Genki IdolVigorously Idolizing
No matter how old I get, I'll always shine here
Tell me, Karen, are you cute today?
You're so cute!
Hey, hey, tell me, is Mr. Hallen cute today?
You're so cute.
I'll always love you, I promise.
I'll always, always love you, too.
Will you love me forever?
Pink, frilly, in the spotlight.
Someday, I'm sure, I'll be all yours
Now I want to sing again Electrolyte Idol
Thank you, everyone, for coming out.
I worked hard again!
Happy birthday, cue you
Happy birthday, Q-You
Happy Birthday Queue you
Thank you.
Too cute
You're so cute.
I'm shaking.
I'm shaking so much.
Oh, my God, I'm shaking so much.
I'm shaking so much!
He's fine, isn't he?
He's so cute!
Here's the album!
I got albums from all the fans.
It's so cute!
So cute. Karen's outfit.
Oh, my God.
It says "Super Karen Day" on it.
So cute!
And this is Karen's choker!
That's right.
I'm sure it's real!
It's a swan costume.
Oh, my God.
Very expensive.
It's so cute.
Thank you very much.
That's so cute.
Congratulations with Karen!
Congratulations to Karen.
We have a very special guest today.
He's here for Karen.
This is her. Come on in.
Happy birthday to Karen.
Thanks for the apple eve.
Wait!
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much.
Cute.
Thank you
I'm so glad.
Thank you, I didn't know.
Yes, well, Happy Birthday, Kanetan!
Thank you!
Then check it out.
A lot.
Wait, wait, wait, too cute.
People are so cute.
Cute.
I'm so happy.
Crack?
What's crack?
Crack.
Crack?
That's so cute.
What is that?
What's that? It's so cute.
Can I have some of that later?
It's so cute.
It's the day we lose. It's normal.
It's the yankest day of the year for us, but it can't be helped.
I'm not sure if my ego's cool with it.
Surprise message. No surprise, that's the rule.
What's your age now? Until then, I had a lot.
I've had a lot of useless encounters and stuff.
I love you so much right now, and I'm so happy for you.
I really love you right now, and I'm really happy for you.
I want to do something stupid. I want to say it, but...
I'd love to do something stupid, I'd love to say, but why not? Why isn't there a little bit of a trial?
I mean, it's not like I don't already feel good.
I guess I'm happy after all.
Because I bought all the answers.
I'm gonna take the trash to the dump, and I'm gonna set off some fireworks.
Let's do it all at once
That's it for us fruit zippers!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
Happy Birthday.
Why do you have that?
What?
Is that...
Fake?Fake?
Real?
Where would I go then?
But I can't? I don't think I can go today.
Is all this real?
No, they're not real. I'll hold them down.
Okay, I'll take this one and the one next to it.
Okay, here we go.
Okay?
Are you okay?
Here we go.
Here you go.
Wow, that's scary.
I want to get a Kulshat.
I want to take a picture of Cruzhat.
Can I just take a side shot?
Is that good?
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
Okay, next.
Okay. - Okay.
Here we go.
Okay, I'm going.
Okay, let's go!
Okay!
Two shots.
Here we go!
No, from here, it's a two-shot.
Here we go.
Yes, I'm going.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Okay, I'm going next.
Yes, I'm going. - Yes, I'm going in. - I'm going in.
I'll let you in. - Yes, I'm going.
Yes, sir.
Cute pair of moni-moni.
Yes, turn around.
Yes, yes, yes. Okay, three to go.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, okay. Yes, last.
Yes, okay.
Okay, I'll go to the side.
Yes, I'll go to the last pose.
Yes, OK
Yes, okay.
Okay, come back.
Oh, I'm not moving.
Here we go.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Wait a minute.
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay, I'll go to the next vertical.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'm so scared!
Okay!
Let's go!
Okay.
I'm going to do the last work.
Thank you for your hard work.
Yes, yes, that was close.
It's all right.
There you are.
Ice Earl.
My shoulder's out.
Don't let him get to you.
Yes, sir.
Here's the video.
Oh, sorry.
It's not good!
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
Your time is up.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I couldn't do it.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Thank you for watching.
You know, you're the cutest thing I've ever seen in my life.
You're the most amazing, amazing, amazing, cheapest thing about me.
And I'm the cutest thing you know.
I noticed that, too.
That's why you're so cute. That's why you're so cute.
That's cute. That's cute. That's cute.
Don't say that. Don't say that about anyone but me.
I can't be anything else.
Thank you for watching.
It's a secret. I'm a wizard.
Ring chic on my cheeks
Lip of the day and kimeki nite
I'm in love with you, I'm in love with you, I'm in love with you, I'm in love with you
I can't do it at all, I can't do it at all, I can't do it at all
Don't stop, don't stop, don't stop
Listen to me, tell me, is the calendar still cute today?
I'll always love you, I promise.I'll always love you, I promise.
I'll always, always love you.
Will you love me forever?